mariowiki.com 2019-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Porplemontage Enterprises, LLC

| 

For Porplemontage Enterprises, LLC  
Effective date: 6/7/2018  
  
---|---  
  
Porplemontage Enterprises, LLC ("Porplemontage Enterprises", "we", "us", or "our") recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of our web services. We created the following policy guidelines with a fundamental respect for our users' right to privacy. Porplemontage Enterprises operates Destinypedia ([https://www.destinypedia.com](https://www.destinypedia.com/)), Halopedia ([https://www.halopedia.org](https://www.halopedia.org/)), Kingdom Hearts Wiki ([https://www.khwiki.com](https://www.khwiki.com/)), Pikipedia ([https://www.pikminwiki.com](https://www.pikminwiki.com/)), Pikmin Fanon ([http://www.pikminfanon.com](http://www.pikminfanon.com/)), SmashWiki ([https://www.ssbwiki.com](https://www.ssbwiki.com/)), Super Mario Boards ([https://www.marioboards.com](https://www.marioboards.com/)), and Super Mario Wiki ([https://www.mariowiki.com](https://www.mariowiki.com/)) — collectively, the "Services". This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Services and the choices you have associated with that data. We use your data to provide and improve our Services. By using any of our Services, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

## Definitions

### Service

A Service is any of the Services operated by Porplemontage Enterprises. This includes but is not limited to Destinypedia ([https://www.destinypedia.com](https://www.destinypedia.com/)), Halopedia ([https://www.halopedia.org](https://www.halopedia.org/)), Kingdom Hearts Wiki ([https://www.khwiki.com](https://www.khwiki.com/)), Pikipedia ([https://www.pikminwiki.com](https://www.pikminwiki.com/)), Pikmin Fanon ([http://www.pikminfanon.com](http://www.pikminfanon.com/)), SmashWiki ([https://www.ssbwiki.com](https://www.ssbwiki.com/)), Super Mario Boards ([https://www.marioboards.com](https://www.marioboards.com/)), and Super Mario Wiki ([https://www.mariowiki.com](https://www.mariowiki.com/)).

### Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

### Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of our Services or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

### Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device (computer or mobile device). For more information about cookies, please visit: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/>

### Data Controller

Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.

### Data Processors (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

### Data Subject (or User)

Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Services and is the subject of Personal Data.

## Types of Data Collected by Porplemontage Enterprises

Porplemontage Enterprises collects information about users when they create an account on our Services and during their participation in certain activities, such as contests and newsletters. When users request pages from our web server, our server automatically collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses. These addresses are used by computers on the network to send the requested pages to users.

### Personal Data

While using our Services, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

#### Email Address

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt-out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information on how our Services are accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Services that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Services and hold certain information. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Services. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Services. Examples of Cookies we use:

  * Session Cookies: We use Session Cookies to operate our Services.
  * Preference Cookies: We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * Security Cookies: We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
  * Advertising Cookies: Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.

##### "Do Not Track" Signals

We do not currently support Do Not Track ("DNT"), however some third-party advertising companies used by Porplemontage Enterprises may support this. Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

## Use of Data

Porplemontage Enterprises uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Services
  * To notify you about changes to our Services
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Services when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Services
  * To monitor the usage of our Services
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers, and general information about other goods, services, and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

### Cookies & Advertising

Porplemontage Enterprises may use user-entered information in combination with site usage information to help display advertisements relevant to users' interests and navigation patterns. Porplemontage Enterprises may use cookies to help in tracking these patterns but does not store or collect any personal data in combination with user-supplied information. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s "help" file. For more information about cookies please visit: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/>

### Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it. Porplemontage Enterprises may process your Personal Data because:

  * We need to perform a contract with you
  * You have given us permission to do so
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights
  * To comply with the law

## Retention of Data

Porplemontage Enterprises will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. Porplemontage Enterprises will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Services, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

## Transfer of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. Porplemontage Enterprises will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Disclosure of Data

### Business Transaction

If Porplemontage Enterprises is involved in a merger, acquisition, or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Porplemontage Enterprises may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

### Legal Requirements

Porplemontage Enterprises may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * Comply with a legal obligation
  * Protect and defend the rights or property of Porplemontage Enterprises
  * Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with our Services
  * Protect the personal safety of users of our Services or the public
  * Protect against legal liability

## Security of Data

Porplemontage Enterprises uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure and to disclose such information only to responsible third parties after permission from the user. The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Porplemontage Enterprises aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  * The right to access, update, or delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update, or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
  * The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
  * The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  * The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable, and commonly-used format.
  * The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Porplemontage Enterprises relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

## Service Providers

We may employ third-party companies and individuals to facilitate our Services ("Service Providers"), to provide our Services on our behalf, to perform Service-related services, or to assist us in analyzing how our Services are used. These third-parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Services.

#### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Services. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on our Services available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

### Advertising

Porplemontage Enterprises may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you when you visit our Services, to help support and maintain our Services. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to our Services and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit: <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/>

#### Google AdSense & DoubleClick Cookie

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Services. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Services or other websites on the Internet. You may opt-out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: <https://adssettings.google.com/>

### Social Media

The collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use social media channels associated with Porplemontage Enterprises and our Services, including but not limited to Discord servers, Facebook pages, Twitter accounts, YouTube channels, and Twitch channels are subject to the privacy policies of those respective platforms. Porplemontage Enterprises is not responsible for the privacy policies of third-party Service Providers.

## Links to Other Websites

Our Services may contain links to other websites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third-party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party websites or services to which we may provide links.

## Contests

By entering contests hosted through any of our Services, users consent to the use of their name or pseudonym in the announcement of the winners on the Service website, and use of their name and likeness for advertising and/or promotional/marketing purposes. Users' contact information may also be used by us to notify users they have won and to confirm their mailing address.

## Children's Privacy

If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data without your consent, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without parental consent, we will take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email: [porple.privacy@gmail.com](mailto:porple.privacy@gmail.com)

Please, no solicitations. We are not looking to make any changes to our advertisement setup.
